youngharlotsacademy.com 2013-05-28

# HarmonyVision Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy and Data Protection  
A note on your privacy

According to the Spanish data protection laws, personal data collected on the Site as provided by You, by registration, purchasing of a membership or other forms, will be used by Manica Media, S.L. to provide You with the services requested and inform You about promotional related activities or new services related to the adult business. By providing us with such data, you consent to such use of such data and any additional use specifically included in the Registration Form.

You may ask us for details on your personal data as hold by us, and you may also ask us to rectify, cancel or refuse such personal data processing by contacting Manica Media, S.L., Pau Claris, 108, atico, Barcelona, Spain, or sending an email to [info@manicamedia.com](mailto:info@manicamedia.com).

We hereby inform you that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or by Court. We do not share personal data and/or information with third parties except when specifically consented by You when registering or by specific request.

We might share information as provided by You with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as payments, orders processing, or maintaining of the Site.

All other visual depictions displayed on this Website are exempt from the provision of 18 U.S.C. section 2257 and 28 C.F.R. 75 because said visual depictions do not consist of depictions of conduct as specifically listed in 18 U.S.C section 2256 (2) (A) through (D), but are merely depictions of non-sexually explicit nudity, or are depictions of simulated sexual conduct, or are otherwise exempt because the visual depictions were created prior to July 3, 1995.
